so this YouTube channel is changing
there are going to be three YouTube
channels one of which is the idea Cafe
which already exists it's one
conversation that I have weekly that is
interwoven with the rest of my journey
and the rest of the conversations I'm
having in order to follow my purpose my
journey towards authenticity and
figuring out who I am finding the
resources that I need to do the projects
that I'm here to do and finding my
people
and so the NTA cafe who crowd democracy
where I'm gonna be showcasing that
journey so that there's a record of it
so that you can see eventually what the
journey was that I knew there was a
place where we got in two minutes inter
woven and you're gonna see it unfold
before your eyes you get to watch it
here and you get to watch me make an ass
of myself saying things like that until
it shows itself and proves itself and
then you get to watch that to see you're
in it on the ground floor and me having
conversations with people about their
projects about their genius the purpose
they're here to do figuring out who they
are and how we answer some of these
questions the new YouTube channel will
be the together all the stuff that's
together tech specific so the live board
meeting the project raising anything
like mastermind groups that we start for
the meta project on how to help people
live their purpose how to gather
resources how to I'm this because I'm
still answering those four questions
that I keep referring to this is what
I'm obsessed with these weeks I'm going
to be showing you the journey having
conversations on this channel idea Cafe
is one conversation that you can see
continually for the same people repeat a
lot that's kind of like the Omega roll
groups and we pick a question and we
take turns answering it you can see the
power of a conversation that I'm
changing they're changing its changing
and it's fun to be part of it's not done
for the audience it's done for the
participation hopefully we can create a
social media
from this designed for that so everybody
has access to that but we'll see I don't
have the capacity capability of making
that or the money at the moment so we're
creating together check the other check
it's going to be its own youtube channel
and this one will focus just on my
journey and the home and conversations
that people want to be made public and
the idea Cafe will be the one set of
conversations that you get to go through
and what hopefully 5-member once that
other channel launches I will put in the
description of this video I can put the
idea cafe in the description of this
video and you're already on grab
democracy so that is the evolution of
YouTube channels and what is happening
Thanks